<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maiya Yu</title>
    <link>http://maiyayu.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Maiya Yu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://maiyayu.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Maiya Yu. You can reach me at mshyu@umich.edu, or at the links in the sidebar I am a current senior (class of 2021) at the University of Michigan College of Literature, Science, and the Arts, where I am majoring in biochemistry and pure mathematics, and minoring in computer science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/research/</guid>
      <description>Research Current Projects The Dual-Dual Expression System Work affiliated with University of Michigan, Department of Pharmacology, Tall Lab My current work focuses on improving methods of purifying G proteins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/tutoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/tutoring/</guid>
      <description>Tutoring Math Lab The University of Michigan Math Lab is not open during summers, but you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to find the times I am in the Math Lab here shortly into Fall 2020!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/coffee/</guid>
      <description>Coffee I am a coffee aficionado and passionate amateur barista. Here are some of my (extremely biased and probably unnecessary) opinions about coffee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Computer Science</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/computer-science/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science My first introduction to computer science came as I was preparing to spend a summer doing computational research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Dip</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/food/green-dip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/food/green-dip/</guid>
      <description>Green Dip Ingredients  Half a bunch fresh cilantro 1/3 cup mayonnaise 1/4 cup ranch dressing Half an avocado Couple turns freshly ground pepper 1 tbsp onion powder 1 tbsp garlic powder Juice of half a lime Olive oil  Instructions Wash and roughly tear cilantro into blender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mango Salsa</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/food/mango-salsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/food/mango-salsa/</guid>
      <description>Mango Salsa Ingredients  2 ripe mangoes, chopped 1/2 bunch cilantro, chopped 2 jalapenos, minced 1 red onion, chopped finely Juice of 2 limes Freshly ground pepper Salt  Instructions Mix chopped produce in a bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mathematics</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/mathematics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/mathematics/</guid>
      <description>Mathematics Although I am a pure math major in the U(M) Math Department, I generally prefer to consider myself an amateur mathematician in the original sense of the word &amp;ndash; I do it for the love of the subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oatmeal Coconut Chocolate Chip Cookies</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/food/oatmeal-coconut-chocolate-chip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/food/oatmeal-coconut-chocolate-chip/</guid>
      <description>Oatmeal Coconut Chocolate Chip Cookies Ingredients  2 sticks softened butter (1 cup) 3/4 cup white sugar 3/4 cup brown sugar 2 eggs 2 tsp vanilla 1/4 tsp coconut flavoring 2 tsp baking powder 1 tsp baking soda 1 tsp salt 1 1/4 tsp cinnamon 2 cups flour 1 1/2 cups oats 1 cup shredded coconut (sweetened is okay) 1 1/2 cups chocolate chips  Instructions Preheat oven to 350F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Origami</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/origami/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/miscellanea/origami/</guid>
      <description>Origami As a seventh grader, I was gifted a Klutz book on origami and an origami-a-day calendar, which set off a fondness for folding paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Ratatouille</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/food/ratatouille/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/food/ratatouille/</guid>
      <description>Quick Ratatouille Ingredients  2 medium zucchini, thinly sliced 2 medium yellow squash, thinly sliced 1 medium eggplant, thinly sliced into half-disks 6 roma tomatoes, thinly sliced Italian seasoning 1 jar tomato basil pasta sauce olive oil  Instructions Preheat oven to 400F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tuscan Bean Toast</title>
      <link>http://maiyayu.me/food/tuscan-bean-toast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://maiyayu.me/food/tuscan-bean-toast/</guid>
      <description>Tuscan Bean Toast Ingredients  2 cans white beans (Great Northern or cannelini) 1 can chopped tomatoes 1/2 bunch kale, washed and roughly torn 1/2 white onion, chopped finely 3 garlic cloves, minced Italian seasoning Olive oil Freshly ground pepper Salt Crusty bread Butter Eggs (optional)  Instructions Heat olive oil in a pan over medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>